嘿，我都打包好可以走了
Hey! I'm all packed and ready to go.
没错，爹地跟乔伊叔叔今天要出门去
That's right. Daddy and Uncle Joey are going on a trip today.
我们要去参加一个在巴贝多的研讨会 你会说“巴贝多”吗？
We're going to a conference in Barbados. Right? Can you say,"Barbados"?
巴贝多
Barbados.
我觉得要你们 到那么远的地方去…
Okay. I've gotta say,it means so much to me that you guys are coming..
听我的演讲，对我真是意义重大
all the way over there to hear me give my speech.
我让要你们高兴一下 我费尽功夫…
And I have a surprise. I had to pull some strings..
帮大家争取到整个研讨会的通行证 没错！
but I was able to get everyone passes to the entire conference. That's right!
这些宝贝可以让你们自由参加所有的 古生物学演讲或是研讨会
These babies will get you into all the paleontology lectures and seminars.
你有什么东西 是可以让我们不用参加的吗？
Do you have anything that will get us out of them?
我们真的很兴奋要听你的演讲 但是其他的时间…
We're excited to hear the speech,but the rest of the time..
我们想要做一些岛上活动
we're gonna want to do island stuff.
大卫或许会想要听几场演说
David will probably want to hear a few lectures.
-没错，因为他是科学家 -不，不
- Right,because he's a scientist. - No,no.
他在明斯克待了八年 如果他在阳光下太久…
He's been in Minsk for eight years. If he gets too much direct sunlight..
他会死的
he'll die.
-好的，我们最好出发了 -是吗？
- Okay,we'd better go. - Yeah?
-那我们明天见 -好的，明天见
- So we'll see you guys tomorrow. - All right,let's do it.
跟查莉一起飞行五个小时，喝几杯酒…
A five-hour flight with Charlie,have a couple drinks..
在毛毯下做一些自然会发生的事
get under that blanket and do what comes natural.
那是毛毯，乔伊，不是隐形大衣
It's a blanket,Joe,not a cloak of invisibility.
巴贝多之行
The.One.In.Barbados
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
主演：寇妮考克斯
主演：丽莎库卓
主演：马修派瑞
主演：麦特勒布兰
主演：大卫修蒙
-哇，这地方真漂亮！ -瞧瞧这些古生物学家！
- Wow,this place is beautiful! - Look at all these paleontologists!
我知道 明天游泳池旁一定有许多苍白的人
I know. There are gonna be some pasty folks by the pool tomorrow.
-我的天啊，我不敢相信你在这里！ -我想我被认出来了
- My God,I can't believe you're here! - I think I've been recognized.
-这常常发生的 -盖勒博士？我真是仰慕你
- This happens all the time. - Dr. Geller? I am such a huge fan.
这倒是从来没有发生过
That never happens.
我多年以来一直很注意你的研究 我等不及要听你的演说了
I've been following your career for years. I can't wait for your keynote speech.
-哇，你太过奖了 -我会很想要你的签名的
- Wow! This is very flattering. - I would love your autograph.
喔，当然
Well,sure.
-亲爱的？ -莎拉
- "Dear..?" - Sarah.
“莎拉，我挖（喜欢）你”
"Sarah. I dig you."
-“罗斯盖勒博士上” -哇，真是太谢谢你了
- "Dr. Ross Geller." - Oh,thank you so much.
不客气，莎拉，让我帮你介绍一下 我同事，魏勒教授
Sure. Sarah,I'd like you to introduce you to my colleague,Professor Wheeler.
-这位是乔伊崔比亚尼 -你是古生物学家吗？
- And this is Joey Tribbiani. - Are you a paleontologist?
不，天啊，不，我是演员
No,God,no,no. I'm an actor.
你或许有看过我演的一出小戏叫做 《那个我们的日子》
You probably recognize me from a little show called The Days of Our Lives.
老兄，只是《我们的日子》
Dude,it's just Days of Our Lives.
没有“那个”
There's no "the."
好的，罗斯，天啊，你…是啊 不，我扮演德瑞克雷莫瑞医生
Okay,Ross. Boy,you.. Yeah. No,no. I play Dr. Drake Ramoray.
-我很抱歉，我家没有电视 -你家没有电视？
- I'm sorry. I don't own a TV. - You don't own a TV?
那你家的家具是摆向哪个方向呢？
What's all your furniture pointed at?
-很荣幸认识你们 -我们也是，莎拉，再见
- Well,it was a pleasure to meet you all. - You too,Sarah.
天啊，这年头谁没有电视呢？
Jeez,who doesn't own a TV?
嗯，事实上，我没有
Well,actually,I don't.
是啊，我的两个月前坏了 还没买新的
Yeah,and mine broke two months ago and I still haven't gotten a new one.
那你们两个还真是来对研讨会了
Well,didn't you two come to the right convention.
大卫，你可以帮个忙吗？
David,can you help me?
我正在跟钱德解释 飞机是怎么漂浮在空中的
I'm trying to explain to Chandler how a plane stays in the air.
当然，那是波诺利原理加上…
Certainly. That's a combination of Bernoulli's Principle..
-牛顿第三运动定律 -知道了吗？
- and Newton's third law of motion. - See?
是啊，那还真是跟 “跟风有关的”一样
Yeah. That's the same as,"It has something to do with wind."
我要去为这次旅行买几样东西
I'm gonna go pick up a few things for the trip.
我也应该走了 明天你们要一起搭计程车到机场吗？
I should go too. Now,tomorrow do you want to share a cab to the airport..
还是说我跟麦克到机场跟你们碰面呢？
or should Mike and I meet you?
麦克？谁是麦克呢？
Mike? Who's Mike?
-麦克是你的前男友 -没错！
- Mike's your ex-boyfriend. - That's right!
哇，我已经完全忘了他了
Oh,yeah. Wow,I had totally forgotten about him.
-难忘往日情怀脱口而出吗？ -不，没关系的，无心之过
- That's a blast from the past,huh? - No,it's okay. Honest mistake.
那真的不代表什么 我是说，你知道的…
It really doesn't mean anything. I mean,you know..
莫妮卡也常常把钱德叫成理查
Monica refers to Chandler as Richard all the time.
-她有吗？ -我们快让你离开吧
- She does? - Let's get you out of here.
至少你也拖我下水了
Well,at least you took me down with you.
我很抱歉，我只是… 我一直在想麦克
I'm so sorry. I just.. I keep thinking about Mike.
我非常喜欢大卫 而且我们在一起很开心
I'm crazy about David,and we're having so much fun together.
为什么我会想念麦克？这真是… 这会消逝的，对吗？
Why? Why do I miss Mike? That's just.. That's gonna go away,right?
-嗯，我猜是吧，总有一天 -是啊
- Well,I guess. In time. - Yeah.
我是说我对理查的感觉 都已经消失了
I mean,my feelings for Richard are certainly gone.
你又来了，是钱德 你对钱德的感觉都已经消失了
You just did it again. Chandler. Your feelings for Chandler are certainly gone.
天啊，菲比还在想麦克吗？
Boy,Phoebe's still pretty hung up on that Mike,huh?
我不会想太多的
I wouldn't read too much into it.
但是女生把你叫成 她前男友的名字…
Still,a girl calls you by her ex-boyfriend's name..
-那不是什么好事，不是吗？ -让我先打断你一下
- that's not a good thing,right? - Let me stop you there.
因为我想我知道这是怎么回事了 我对给人建议不太行
Because I think I see where this is going. I'm not very good at giving advice.
如果你想知道披萨的馅料或是…
See,if you want advice,go to Ross or Monica. Or Joey..
为何尿尿时有灼热感之类的建议，那就去找罗斯或是 莫妮卡或是乔伊
for advice about pizza toppings or a burning sensation when you pee.
很抱歉，我只是希望能做点什么 你知道吗？
I'm sorry,I just wish there was something I could do,you know?
-嗯，你知道菲比… -真的，我们要这样吗？
- Well,you know Phoebe.. - Seriously,we're gonna do this?
很抱歉，我只希望我能让她忘了麦克
I'm sorry,I just wish I could make her forget about Mike already.
-菲比跟麦克为什么分手呢？ -因为他的阴茎太大了
- Why did Phoebe and Mike break up? - Because his penis was too big.
抱歉，那才是我擅长的事
I'm sorry. That's the kind of thing I do.
他们分手是因为麦克不想要结婚
They broke up because Mike didn't want to get married.
如果让菲比知道 你对婚姻没有异议呢？
What if you let Phoebe know you'd be open to marriage?
太棒了，太棒了，我会跟她求婚
That's great. That's great. I'll propose to her.
什么？
What?
反正我迟早都会这么做的
I was probably going to do it at some point.
-不，我没有说现在 -为何不呢？这实在太聪明了
- No,I didn't mean now. - Well,why not? It's brilliant.
再见，麦克，我们婚礼见，老兄
"Goodbye,Mike. We'll see you at the wedding,fella.
我们可能也不会 邀请你参加婚礼，但是…
Well,we probably won't invite you to the wedding,but.."
-衷心地谢谢你，钱德 -你不用客气
- Well,thank you,Chandler. Sincerely. - Well,you're welcome.
很高兴能够帮得上忙
Glad I could help.
-你认为我该怎么求婚呢？ -我在假装阅读
- How do you think I should propose? - I'm pretending to read here.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你好吗？嘿，你好吗？
Yeah. How you doing? Hey,how are you?
你说你要穿丁字裤的，丁字裤呢？
You said you were gonna wear a thong. Where's the thong?
我不是说丁字裤 我是说夹脚凉鞋
I didn't mean a thong. I meant thongs.
你应该要说清楚的
You really should have been more clear about that.
你们不会相信我在楼下看到谁
You're never gonna guess who I just saw downstairs.
小甜甜布兰妮！
Britney Spears!
是啊，她从来不会错过 这些研讨会的
Yeah. She never misses these conferences.
-我刚刚看到肯尼斯史华兹博士！ -喔，我的天啊！
- No,I just saw Dr. Kenneth Schwartz! - Oh,my God!
-我知道 -你有跟他说话吗？
- I know! - Did you talk to him?
是喔，我要跟 肯尼斯史华兹说什么呢？
Oh,yeah. What am I gonna say to Kenneth Schwartz?
你可以说“嗨，肯尼 为什么你不是小甜甜布兰妮呢？”
You could say,"Hey,Kenny,how come you're not Britney Spears?"
-你准备好要走了吗？ -你现在就要走了吗？
- You ready to go? - You're gonna go now?
-我以为我们可以在一起度过 -我不行，我整天都有研讨会
- I thought we could hang out. - I can't. I have seminars all day.
我答应罗斯我会看看他的演说稿
I promised Ross I'd look at his speech.
但是或许我们晚点可以共进晚餐 在阳台外面，会很浪漫的
But maybe we could have dinner later? Out on the balcony? It'll be romantic.
你可以穿丁字裤吗？
Will you wear a thong?
你穿我就穿
I will if you will.
你的交换条件真是奇怪
You got yourself a very weird deal.
我很好，我晚餐已经有安排了
I'm good. I have dinner plans.
-你一个人可以吗？ -是的，可以
- So you gonna be okay? - Yeah,yeah.
我有很多事可以做 我要去海滩，去游泳
I got tons of stuff I could do. I'm gonna hit the beach,go swimming.
乔伊，你有看看外面吗？
Joe,have you looked outside?
没有，为什么呢？
No. Why?
-天啊 -这里有室内游泳池
- Oh,man. - There's an indoor pool.
-你可以在那边游泳 -是啊
- You could swim there. - Yeah.
我没有要游泳，我是要去挖洞的
I wasn't gonna swim. I was gonna dig a hole.
麦克那件事真是有趣，我不知道…
That Mike thing was interesting. I don't know what's gonna happen..
-菲比跟大卫之间会发生什么事 -我知道，想要个提示吗？
- with Phoebe and David. - I do. Want a hint,huh?
我愿意
I do.
好的，我可以感到 这是什么文字游戏的
Okay,I'm sensing this is some kind of wordplay..
因为你已经有点 无法控制的兴奋发红了
because you are pink with barely controlled glee.
-大卫要跟菲比求婚了 -什么？为什么？
- David's gonna propose to Phoebe. - What? Why?
因为我们本来在谈 有哪些他可以赢过麦克的方式
Because we were talking about ways he could beat Mike..
而我告诉他菲比想要结婚
and I told him Phoebe wanted to get married.
钱德，我们已经谈过了
Chandler,we have talked about this.
你不可以给别人建议的！
You are not supposed to give people advice!
你不能说一些什么 不适宜的笑话就好了吗？
Couldn't you have made some inappropriate joke?
我说了！
I did!
一个阴茎的笑话！
A penis one!
说明一下，我说的有什么不对的呢？
Just so I know,what was so wrong about what I said?
他们才交往几个星期而已
They've only been going out for a few weeks.
菲比还无法忘记麦克 我想她会拒绝的
Phoebe is completely hung up on Mike. I mean,she'll say no..
然后大卫的心会碎 他们会很难复合
David's heart will be broken,it'll be too hard for them to recover..
而然后菲比又会是孤单的一个人
and then Phoebe will end up alone again.
天啊，真是糟糕的建议
Man,that's some bad advice.
感谢上帝你们来了
Oh,hey. Thank God. You guys are here.
-怎么了？ -这里的一切都不对劲
- What's going on? - Everything is upside-down here.
整天都在下雨，没有人看电视 而且罗斯还很有名气
It rains all day long and nobody watches TV,and Ross is famous.
我不想要惊动大家…
I don't want to alarm anybody..
但是莫妮卡的头发 比下飞机时大了一倍
but Monica's hair is twice as big as it was when we landed.
好了，当我去高湿度地区的时候…
Okay. When I go places with high humidity..
头发就会比较蓬松，好吗？
it gets a little extra body,okay?
那就是为什么我们的蜜月照 看起来是我跟戴安娜罗丝（黑人女歌手）
That's why our honeymoon photos look like me and Diana Ross.
我带你们去登记住房
I'll show you guys where to check in.
亲爱的，你可以确定我们可以拿到 超大尺寸的床吗？
Oh,honey? Can you make sure we get a king-size bed?
大卫，也帮我们确定一下 还有看看他们有没有心型的床
Oh,David,get one for us too. Oh,and see if they have a heart-shaped one.
而且天花板上要有镜子
And with mirrors on the ceiling.
还有确定我们的房间 不要在他们的隔壁
And make sure our room isn't next to theirs.
喔，你们真幸运 有人陪你们到这里
Oh,you guys are so lucky you're here with people.
我真想跟某人分享这一切
I'd love to share this with someone.
亲爱的，你有我们，我们爱你
Oh,honey,you have us. We love you.
太好了，你们谁要跟我睡？
Okay,which one of you is gonna sleep with me?
这是个很浪漫的地方
You know,it's just such a romantic place.
我只希望可以跟一个男人共度
I just wish I could share it with a guy.
-不是乔伊 -不是乔伊，不是
- Not Joey. - Not Joey. No.
-我只是在垂涎钱德 -是啊，没错
- I was just lusting after Chandler. - Yeah,right.
我今晚要跟菲比求婚了
So.. I'm proposing to Phoebe tonight.
今晚？
Tonight?
订婚戒指不是应该要有钻石的吗？
Isn't an engagement ring supposed to have a diamond?
喔，在这里
Oh,there it is.
是啊，一个失败的科学家 并没有你想像的赚的多
Yes,well,being a failed scientist doesn't pay quite as well as you might think.
那是七十分之一克拉
That's one-seventieth of a carat.
清晰度是很差
And the clarity is quite poor.
很好
Nice.
-莫妮卡，我可以跟你谈一下吗？ -好的
- Monica,can I talk to you for a second? - Okay.
大卫要在今晚跟菲比求婚
David's gonna propose to Phoebe tonight.
瞧瞧这就是你给别人建议的后果
See what happens when you give people advice?
-我希望你有告诉他不可以 -那又会是一个建议了！
- Well,I hope you told him not to. - That would be advice!
好的，没关系，让我来处理
Okay,fine. I'll handle this.
-菲比？ -怎样？
- Phoebe? - Yeah?
-我需要跟你谈谈 -你要离开你的主宰了吗？
- I need to talk to you. - Are you leaving the Supremes?
我老公刚给了你男友 一个很糟糕的建议
Okay,my husband just gave your boyfriend some very bad advice.
大卫今晚要跟你求婚了
David's gonna propose to you tonight.
哇，真的吗？
Wow,really?
这实在太棒了！
That's fantastic!
什么？你是说真的吗？你想嫁给他？
What? Are you serious? You want to marry him?
-那麦克呢？ -好的，你要我嫁给麦克是吗？
- What about Mike? - Oh,okay,you want me to marry Mike?
让我们把他塞住嘴巴 用手铐铐住他
Let's just gag him and handcuff him..
然后逼他踏上红毯，好吗？
and force him down the aisle,okay?
我已经可以预见到 “麦克，你愿意娶菲比吗？”
I can just see it. "Mike,do you take Phoebe?"
你知道吗？真是每个女孩的梦想
You know? It's every girl's dream.
你真的认为嫁给别人是对的？
Do you really think marrying someone else is the right answer?
当然，听着，最重要的是 我爱麦克…大卫！
Sure. Look,okay,bottom line? I love Mike.. David!
大卫！我爱大卫！
David! I love David.
别那样看我，Roseanne Roseannadanna（吉尔达・瑞德创造的字符，吉尔达的发型与莫妮卡相似）
Don't look at me that way,Roseanne Roseannadanna.
借由使用中央标准扫描法跟电脑影像 我们可以以非常真实的方式…
"By using CT scans and computer imaging,we can,in a very real way..
将中生代时期带进二十一世纪
bring the Mesozoic Era into the 21st century."
太棒了
It's great.
你真的这么认为吗？
Yeah,you really think so?
你将成为此次研讨会的焦点
You'll be the hit of the conference.
明天还会更好
It'll be even better tomorrow..
因为我不会一直被乔伊打断…
because I won't be constantly interrupted by Joey..
一直来检查我枕头上 是不是有放巧克力
checking to see if they put chocolates on my pillow yet.
-你们好 -巧克力还没送来
- Hey,guys. - The chocolates aren't here.
该死的！
Damn it!
罗斯刚念了他的演讲稿给我听 真是精彩
Ross just read me his speech. It's fantastic.
在电脑里面吗？因为我也想读读看
Oh,is it on the computer? Because I'd love to give it a read.
如果你想要查电子邮件就说吧
If you want to check your e-mail,just ask.
什么？我可以吗？
What? May I?
那个雨是怎么回事呢？盖勒 我是说当我报名恐龙周末的时候…
What's with the rain,Geller? I mean,when I signed up for dino week..
没有人说过现在是雨季
nobody said anything about it being monsoon season.
-雨季是六月到十二月 -现在不是时候，查莉
- The wet season is June to December. - It's not the time,Charlie.
哎呀，糟糕！亲爱的上帝，不！
Oh,no. No,no! Dear God,no!
怎么了？有人比你抢先拍下茶壶吗？
What,did someone outbid you for the teapot?
秘密茶壶
Secret teapot.
你的电脑，我不知道怎么… 一切都不见了
Your computer. I don't know what.. Everything's gone.
-你是什么意思呢？ -一定是病毒
- What do you mean? - Must be a virus.
我想它把你的硬盘全清掉了
I think it erased your hard drive.
什么？我的天啊！ 你干了什么好事？
What? Oh,my God. What did you do?
一个我不认识的人寄了封信给我 然后我打开了它
Someone I don't know sent me an e-mail and I opened it.
-为什么？为什么你要打开？ -那上面又没有写“这是病毒”
- Why? Why would you open it? - Well,it didn't say,"This is a virus."
-那上面写什么？ -“裸体的…”
- What did it say? - "Nude.."
“安娜库尔尼科娃（网坛美女）的照片”
"Pictures of Anna Kournikova."
-我很抱歉 -我该怎么办呢？
- I'm so sorry. - What am I gonna do?
-我的讲稿不见了！ -没有不见
- My speech is gone! - It's not gone.
我相信你有打印出来，你有拷贝吗？
I'm sure you printed out a copy. You have a hard copy?
不，我没有！
No,I don't!
那你现在一定很气自己
Well,you must be pretty mad at yourself right now.
-真的不见了吗？ -是的
- It's really gone? - Yep.
我想要谢谢你们过来这里…
I'd like to thank you guys for coming down here..
抱怨这些雨 然后毁了我的事业前途
to complain about the rain and ruin my career.
-我觉得糟透了 -你的确应该
- I just feel awful. - Yeah,you should.
安娜库尔尼科娃的裸照？ 她根本连什么大奖都没赢过
Nude pictures of Anna Kournikova? She's never even won a major tournament.
我是有试过比利・简・金（20世纪70年代的网坛名将），但是…
Well,I tried Billie Jean King,but..
你知道吗？你跟莫妮卡一样都有那种 我想要杀死你的表情
You know,you and Monica have the same I'm-gonna-kill-you look.
我通常可以亲她一下 就逃过一劫
I can usually make it go away by kissing her.
滚出去
Get out.
我工作的电脑也常常发生这种事
You know,this happens all the time to my computer at work.
-那你怎么办呢？ -我通常会…
- What do you do? - I usually go..
到别人的电脑上 玩俄罗斯方块
play Tetris on somebody else's computer.
我不敢相信发生这种事
I can't believe this is happening.
我明天就要演讲了
I have to give the keynote speech tomorrow.
我要站在所有人面前，我要说什么呢？
I have to stand up in front of all these people. What am I gonna say?
你可以用我背下来 参加试演的那段话
You can use a speech I memorized for auditions.
我不认为你在《星球大战》里的独白 可以对我有所帮助
I don't think your monologue from Star Wars is gonna help me right now.
罗斯，不会有问题的 我听过你的演讲
Ross,we can solve this. I just heard your speech.
-我们可以重建它，我们有一整晚 -什么？你真的认为我们办得到吗？
- We can re-create it. We've got all night. - What,you really think we can do that?
等等，乔伊跟我应该要共进晚餐的
Oh,wait. Joey and I are supposed to have dinner.
别担心，我知道罗斯需要你
Don't worry about that. I mean,Ross needs you.
瑞秋跟我会留下来尽量帮忙
Rachel and I will stay and help any way we can.
好的，我们开始吧
All right. Okay,let's do it.
我知道我们一开始 是讨论碳年代测定法的缺点
Well,I know we start by discussing the shortcomings of carbon dating.
然后我接着解说很明显地什么是…
And then I move on to what is clearly the defining moment..
中生代的决定时刻，原始大陆的分裂 不是吗？
of the Mesozoic Era,the breakup of Pangaea. Hello?
然后接下来是三叠纪的概观
And then there's the overview of the Triassic.
有可能这一切都是在 很远的银河发生的吗（星球大战的台词）？
Any chance any of this happened in a galaxy far,far away?
-嗨？ -好了，麦克？
- Hello? - Okay,Mike?
闹够了，你爱菲比，而她也爱你
Enough is enough. You love Phoebe,and she loves you.
所以不要再说什么不想要结婚的话了
So get over your I-never-wanna-get-married thing..
赶快站出来！
and step up!
你是谁？
Who is this?
我是莫妮卡，菲比的朋友
This is Monica,Phoebe's friend.
莫妮卡，你又回到我生命中 真是太好了
Sure,Monica. So good to have you back in my life.
听着，菲比跟大卫复合了
Listen,Phoebe is back with David.
他即将要求婚，而她将会答应
He's gonna propose,and she's gonna say yes..
但是我知道 她真正想要的是跟你在一起
but I know she really wants to be with you.
他要求婚了？
He's gonna propose?
很抱歉，你说什么呢？ 该死的头发遮住我听不到！
I'm sorry,did you say something? I can't hear through all this damned hair!
如果菲比想要嫁给大卫，那就去吧
If Phoebe wants to marry David,she should.
我不会从中作梗，你也不应该
I'm not gonna stand in the way of that. Neither should you.
你不用告诉我该怎么做 我来告诉你怎么做
You don't tell me what to do. I tell you what to do.
打电话给她，她在巴贝多的天堂饭店
Just call her. She's at the Paradise Hotel in Barbados.
对了，你也有卷发
And while I've got you,you've got curly hair.
在湿气重的地方你怎么办呢？
What do you do in the humidity?
该死的！
Damn it!
-嗯，我希望你很快乐 -我也希望你很快乐
- Well,I hope you're happy. - I hope you're happy too,honey.
菲比会答应大卫的求婚
Phoebe's going to say yes to David.
-这就是你爱管闲事的结果 -菲比要答应？太棒了
- That's what happens when you meddle. - Phoebe's gonna say yes? That's great.
不，一点也不，她还爱着麦克
No,it's not. She's still in love with Mike.
-那不会有什么结果的吗？ -没有，我已经打过电话了
- There's no chance that will work? - No,I called.
-不会发生的 -八婆！八婆！
- It's not gonna happen. - Meddler! Meddler!
如果你不先多管闲事…
If you hadn't meddled to start with..
那我就不用插手进来管事了
then I wouldn't have had to go in and meddle myself.
不管我们插手多深 我们都没有办法补救…
No matter how much we meddle,we'll never be able to unmeddle..
你一开始多管闲事惹出来的祸！
the thing that you meddled up in the first place!
这场假期真是烂！
This vacation sucks!
（欢迎古生物学家们）
我好无聊
I'm so bored.
愚蠢的雨，我们什么都做不了
Stupid rain. We can't do anything.
我带了些书来，我们可以阅读
Well,I brought some books. We could read.
嘿，还没糟糕到那个地步
Hey,it hasn't come to that yet.
嘿，等一下
Hey,hey,hey,don't mind if I do.
对不起，先生，这些是给药学研讨会的
I'm sorry,sir,these are for the pharmaceutical convention.
你想要去参加研讨会吗？
You feel like going to a convention?
-我们不行，我们不是药剂师 -我知道我们不是…
- We can't. We're not pharmacists. - I know we're not..
但是法兰克马迭欧跟伊娃齐罗欧…
but Frank Madaio and Eva Trorro..
温芭还是…
Womba
-凯特米勒 -就是凯特米勒
- Kate Miller. - Kate Miller it is.
-好的 -喔，很好…
- Okay. - Oh,good..
而这将是我这周末 仅能有的性接触了
And that's the most sex I'm gonna have this weekend.
如果是这样 我应该确定它粘的够牢吗？
Well,in that case,should I make sure it's on real good?
谢谢你
Thank you.
那么，凯特…
So,Kate..
药局这一行好玩吗？
how's the pharmacy game treating you?
嗯，法兰克，我告诉你，很难喔
Well,Frank,I tell you,it's rough.
我是说，是我的问题还是说医生写的字 都越来越难读了呢？
I mean,is it me or is doctors' handwriting getting harder and harder to read?
我知道，我知道
I know,I know.
我告诉你
I tell you.
但是好处是 我们可以穿那些白色外衣…
But on the plus side,we get to wear those white coats..
-然后站在非常高的柜台后面 -对，是没错
- and stand behind that really tall counter. - Oh,that's true.
你是《我们的日子》里的乔伊崔比亚尼
You're Joey Tribbiani from Days of Our Lives.
终于有人认出我了
Finally,someone recognizes me. Okay.
是《那个我们的日子》
And it's The Days of Our Lives.
-贾姬，是他 -是的，贾姬，是我，过来吧
- Jackie,it is him. - Yeah,Jackie,it's me. Come on over.
天啊，这真是大惊喜！
Oh,my God,this is so exciting!
你为什么会在这里呢？
So why are you here?
我正在研习一部 关于药剂师电影的新角色
I'm doing research for a role in a new movie about pharmacists.
是的，片名叫《爱的处方》
Yeah,it's called Prescription for Love.
-很好 -是的
- Nice. - Yeah.
这是我朋友瑞秋 她也有在这电影中演出
This is my friend Rachel. She's in the movie too.
我是女演员
I'm an actress.
电影内容是什么呢？
So,what's the movie about?
我扮演英俊有男子气概的药剂师
Well,I play the handsome,macho pharmacist..
而瑞秋是我的学生
and Rachel is my student..
她想要学习一切关于…
who wants to learn all about..
-药学的知识 -对
pharmacing.
而且我一开始是很害羞的…
And,see,I'm shy at first..
但是然后我把眼镜拿掉 然后变得很性感，知道吧
but then,I take off my glasses and become sexy,you know.
然后有一些裸露戏，但是是很有格调的
And there's some nudity,but it's very tastefully done.
我在剧中的裸露可是一点都没有格调
My nudity in the film is not tasteful at all.
所以你们是在做研究？
So you're doing research?
-你对我们有什么问题吗？ -我当然有
- Do you have any questions for us? - I sure do.
那个人是去哪 拿那个大杯粉红色的饮料？
Where'd that guy get the big,pink drink?
喔，然后你开始谈将中生代世纪…
Oh,and then you said that thing about bringing the Mesozoic Era..
带到二十一世纪
into the 21st century.
对，就这样吗？
Well,yeah. That's it?
这就是整份演讲稿
That's it. That's the whole speech.
-是的 -天啊，我们办到了
- Yeah. - Oh,my God. We did it.
事实上是我办到了，罗斯 你对自己演讲稿的记忆真是少到惊人
Actually,I did it,Ross. You remembered shockingly little of your own speech.
是的，但是我倒是用沐浴产品 做了个金字塔
Yes,but I did make a pyramid out of the bath products.
这真是惊人，谢谢，真是很谢谢你
Oh,this is amazing. Thank you. Thank you so much.
这真是漂亮的项链
That's a pretty necklace.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们庆祝一下吧？要香槟吗？
Hey,what do you say we celebrate? Champagne?
好啊，软木塞留着，这样我们就可以 把瓶子装满水…
Yeah! Save the cork,and that way,we can fill the bottle with water..
然后再放回去他们就不会收钱了
and put it back so they don't charge you.
我的天啊，我爱你
Oh,my God,I love you.
艾玛这张照片真是可爱 而这是你儿子…
This is such a cute picture of Emma. And is this your son..
还是你会带在身上 某个小男孩照片呢？
or just some kid whose picture you bring on vacation?
那是班，我第一次婚姻所生的儿子
That's Ben,my son from my first marriage.
-你第一次婚姻？ -是的
- Your first marriage? - Yeah.
你结过不只一次婚吗？
You've been married more than once?
没有
No.
那你为什么离婚呢？
So why'd you break up?
嗯，因为…
Oh,it was..
很复杂的，她是…
It's complicated,you know? She was..
同性恋
gay.
事实上并没有这么复杂
Actually,it's not that complicated.
我的天啊
Oh,my God.
这实在太酷了！
This is so cool!
好的，为这怪事兴奋是很奇怪的事
Okay. Odd thing to get excited about.
不是，只是我曾经跟一个男的订婚过 而他最后竟然是同志
No,it's just that I was engaged to a guy who turned out to be gay.
嘿，击掌吧！
Hey! High-five!
你有没有觉得没有看出 端倪实在是很笨呢？
Didn't you feel so stupid that you didn't see the signs?
我未婚夫总是跟 他的“网球球友”一起度周末
My fiance was always going on long weekends with his "tennis partner."
我老婆有一年跟一个朋友 天天都到健身房健身
My wife had a workout friend she went to the gym with every day for a year.
她也没有变瘦
She didn't get any fitter.
-每个人都说“我早就知道了” -我知道
- Everybody's like,"I knew all along." - I know.
如果知道，怎么不告诉我呢？ 我是说只要打电话，留个纸条什么的
If you knew,why didn't you tell me? I mean,call,leave a note.
“嗨，只是过来告诉你 你老婆是同性恋”
"Hi. Just dropped by to say your wife's gay."
-我知道 -然后…
- I know. - And then..
然后你试着在困境中求生存…
And then you try to make the best of a bad situation..
所以你提出三人行的建议
so you float the idea of a threesome.
我没有那样做
I didn't do that.
我也没有
Me neither.
谁会知道呢？药剂师们真好玩
Well,who knew? Pharmacists are fun.
我知道，那位老太太 最后都已经准备要带你回家了
I know. That old lady at the end was ready to take you home.
这世界的药还是不够的，瑞秋
Not enough pills in the world,Rach.
那你呢？你才是单身的人 有没有看到喜欢的人呢？
What about you,huh? You're the single one. See anybody in there you like?
让我想想，那个跟我 说过话的大个儿…
Well,let's see. There was that really big guy that I was talking to..
有着很不错的胸部
with the really nice breasts.
那在家呢？ 有什么吗？你有喜欢的人吗？
But what about back home? Anything going on there? Anybody you like?
没有
No.
-有的，你脸红了 -没有，我没有脸红
- There is. You're blushing. - No,I'm not blushing..
这是晒伤的
and I'm sunburned.
因为下雨的缘故
From,you know,the rain.
你喜欢某人，告诉我是谁
You like someone. Tell me who.
-告诉我是谁，说啦 -不，乔伊
- Tell me who it is. Come on. - No. Joey.
你喜欢谁呢？你别想轻易躲掉
Who do you like? You're not getting away that easy.
-你喜欢谁呢？ -乔伊，别这样
- Who do you like? - Joey,come on!
没什么大不了的，你知道吗？ 又不是说会发生什么事
It doesn't matter,you know? It's not like anything's gonna happen.
什么？为什么不呢？ 瑞秋，有谁你得不到呢？
What? Why not? Rach,who can you not get?
好，你真想知道是谁吗？
Okay. Okay. You really want to know who it is?
-是的，是谁呢？ -你真的想？
- Yeah. Who is it? - Do you?
-嘿 -嗨
- Oh,hey.
-嗨 -我才刚留言给你
- I just left you a message.
罗斯跟我刚要去吃点东西…
Ross and I were gonna go grab a bite..
但是既然你在这里 我们可以共用晚餐了
but now that you're here,we could have that dinner.
没错！当然 演讲稿写完了吗？
Right! Of course. Hey,did you guys finish the speech?
是的，完成了 我们完成了，非常谢谢
Yep! We got it. We got it. Thank you so much.
-我很愉快 -是啊
- I had a great time. - Yeah.
这还没完，因为我真的想知道…
This isn't over,because I really want to know..
以后，以后
Later. Later.
-那我们走吧？ -好的
- So shall we? - Yeah.
-好的 -晚安
- Okay. - Good night.
晚安
Good night.
-好的，晚安 -晚安，罗斯
- Okay,good night. - Good night,Ross.
我不敢相信她会答应
I can't believe she's gonna say yes to David.
她很明显还是爱着麦克
She's clearly in love with Mike.
你看起来这样子 实在很难把你的话当真
You know,it's very hard to take you seriously when you look like that.
我们可以点瓶香槟吗？
Could we have a bottle of champagne,please?
我手头有点紧，所以有没有本地…
And I'm kind of on a budget,so if you have anything local..
或是加拿大的香槟就可以了
or Canadian.
菲比，我要说一些话
Phoebe,I have something I want to say.
天啊，他要开口了 我看不下去，我们走
Oh,God,he's gonna do it. I cannot watch this. Let's go.
我想我们还有时间 你有听过他说话吗？
I think we have time. Have you heard him talk?
“菲比，我将会很荣幸如果…” 说快点，大卫
"Phoebe,I would be honored if.." Spit it out,David!
菲比
Phoebe.
你实在是太好了，我们分开的时候 实在无法让人忍受
You're an amazing woman,and the time we spent apart was unbearable.
当然明斯克卫生设施员工的 罢工让情况更糟
Of course,the sanitation strikes in Minsk didn't help.
当然，好的，是的
Sure. Okay. Yeah.
但是现在我们又一起了 我再也不想分开了
But,well,now that we're together again,I don't ever want to be apart.
所以…
So to that end..
-喔，我的天啊，麦克 -事实上，我是大卫
- Oh,my God,Mike. - It's David,actually.
不，麦克在这里
No,Mike's here.
嘿，麦克
Oh,hey,Mike.
嗨，大卫
Hi,David.
钱德，莫妮… 哇！
Chandler. Monic.. Oh!
是湿气！
It's the humidity!
-嗨，菲比 -你在这里做什么呢？
- Hi,Phoebe. - What are you doing here?
我有个问题必须要问你
I have a question I need to ask you.
我也有个问题要问她
I have a question I was kind of gonna ask her myself.
我了解，但是在你那样做之前 她真的需要先听我说
Yeah,I understand,but before you do,she really needs to hear this.
好的
Okay.
-你要坐我的座位吗？ -事实上会很好
- Would you care for my seat as well? - Actually,yeah,that'd be great.
很公平，你一路这么远赶来
Well,that's fair,you've had a long trip.
菲比，我爱你
Phoebe,I love you.
我过去几个月非常思念你
I've missed you so much these last few months.
我原以为我们分开是有好理由的
I thought we were apart for a good reason..
但是我发现根本没有够好的理由…
but I realized that there was no reason good enough..
能够让我不与你共度下半辈子
to keep me from spending the rest of my life with you.
有点毁了我将要说的话
Kind of steps on the toes of what I was going to say.
抱歉，大卫 但是她真的有需要知道这些
I'm sorry,David,but she really has to know this.
好的，但是之后 我要在外面跟你单挑
All right,but after this,I want to see you outside.
如果外面停止下雨的话
If it stops raining.
你是我遇过最不可思议的女人
You're the most incredible woman I've ever met.
我怎么能够失去你呢？ 我现在并没有戒指
How could I lose you? Now,I don't actually have a ring.
-我有戒指 -我不会在这时候炫耀，老兄
- I have a ring. - I wouldn't brag about that,big guy.
但是，菲比…
But,Phoebe..
你愿意嫁给我吗？
will you marry me?
不
No.
我爱你，但是我从不需要你求婚
I love you,but I never needed a proposal from you.
我只需要知道我们之间是有发展的
I just needed to know we were headed somewhere.
-我们是有未来的 -我们可以有任何你想要的未来
- That we had a future. - We can have any future you want.
好的，我要走了
Okay,well,I'm gonna take off.
大卫，我很抱歉，我好抱歉
David,I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
让我知道一下，如果我先问了？
Just so I know,if I had asked first..?
我有可能会答应，但是那是不对的
Yeah,I might have said yes,but that would've been wrong.
你不用解释，没关系
Please,you don't have to explain.
我是说 如果我当初没有去明斯克…
I mean,perhaps if I hadn't gone to Minsk..
我们之间可能就没问题了 而我也不会毁了我的事业
things would have worked out for us,and I wouldn't have ruined my career.
或是因冻疮而失去那只脚趾
Or lost that toe to frostbite.
那是趟好旅程
It was a good trip.
-我现在可以拥抱你吗？ -喔，可以
- Is it okay if I hug you now? - Oh,yes.
就是因为我们的多管闲事，好吗？
Because of our meddling! All right?
这样不是很好吗？如此安静 我可以整天都躺在这里
Oh,isn't this nice? It's so quiet. I could just lie here all day.
我知道
Oh,I know.
-打开窗帘！打开窗帘！ -我们的房间是相通的还真不错呢
- Open your drapes! Open your drapes! - So glad we got adjoining rooms.
-太阳出来了！ -嘿！记得我有眼角膜吗？
- The sun is out! - Hey! Remember when I had corneas?
赶快去游泳池占位子
Go to the pool and reserve chairs.
-我会拿杂志跟防晒乳液 -罗斯的演讲再四十五分就开始了
- I will get the magazines and the lotion. - Ladies? Ross' speech is in 45 minutes.
-不！ -该死的！
- No! - Damn it!
墙壁很薄的，你们这些人
Walls are pretty thin,guys.
我们必须考量最近磁共振造影资料 与去氧核糖核酸测试资料…
"Then we have to weigh the data from recent MRI scans and DNA testing..
而这些对多年来的碳年代 测定资料收集方式形成了一些疑点
which call into question information gathered from years of carbon dating."
瞧瞧那个坐在游泳池畔 享受日光浴的女人
Look at the woman sitting out by the pool getting tan.
她的皮都有皱纹了，我真是忌妒！
She's all leathery and wrinkled. I'm so jealous!
最后，有最近 许多丰富新物种的发现
"Finally,factor in the profusion of new species recently discovered.
巨兽龙
Giganotosaurus.
-阿根廷龙 -更不用提冷龙
- Argentinosaurus." - Not to mention Coldsaurus.
而这些只是草食性的 我还没有要提到肉食性的
"And that's just the herbivores. I'm not even gonna discuss the carnivores.
他们的头都已经是太大了
Their heads are already too big.
这是蛮讽刺的 因为他们的大脑却是发育不良的
Which is ironic,considering their stunted cerebral development."
真的吗？
Really?
但是撇开玩笑不谈，这是相同于…
"But all kidding aside,in much the same way..
匠人曾被认为是直立人（音近勃起）的 另一个分支
that Homo ergaster is thought to be a separate species from Homo erectus.."
-什么？ -他说勃起
- What? - He said "erectus."
-你在开玩笑吗？ -不，他是真的那样说
- You're kidding,right? - No,he really said it.
而当然有许多很大的差异…
"And while there are certainly vast differences..
介于这些中生代化石 跟此直立人例子
between these Mesozoic fossils and the example of Homo erectus.."
勃起？
Erectus?
-同性恋（音同人种） -没错
- Homo. - Right.
“以非常真实的方式，我们可以 将中生代时期带入二十一世纪”
"In a very real way,we can bring the Mesozoic Era into the 21st century."
谢谢
Thank you.
-真的很棒 -谢谢你们
- Really great. - Oh,thanks,guys.
我认为很精采，我是杰维斯欧伯劳 康乃尔大学
I thought it was wonderful. Jarvis Oberblau. Cornell.
你突显出来的议题 尤其是你是这样的年轻而且…
I mean,the ideas you put forth,and from someone so young and..
好的，现在我们只是在握着手
Okay,now we're just holding hands.
好的，我们要去海滩了 演讲真的很棒
Alrighty. We're gonna hit the beach. That was really great.
-谢谢 -是啊，而且很有趣
- Oh,thank you. - Yeah. Oh,and so funny.
-放轻松点 -好的，谢谢，非常谢谢
- Take it easy. - All right,thanks. Thanks so much.
我无法告诉你 你们在此对我意义有多大
I can't tell you how much it means that you were here.
你在开玩笑吗？我们不可能会错过的
You kidding? We wouldn't have missed it.
我回来了
I'm back.
好的，失陪一下好吗？
Okay. Well,excuse me?
-怎么样？ -你真是不可思议
- Well? - You were incredible.
你完全迷住了他们了
You blew them away.
我无法告诉你在人群中 看到你的脸有多棒
I can't tell you how great it was to look in the crowd and see your face.
我是说 你知道你嘴巴在跟着我念吗？
I mean,did you know you were mouthing the words along with me?
-我没有 -不，没关系
- I was not. - No,it's okay.
那让我觉得很像摇滚巨星
It made me feel like a rock star.
我的天啊 我跟你是一伙的
Oh,my God. I'm your groupie.
我最好不要在房间里 发现你脱光光喔
Hey,I better not find you naked in my hotel room.
哎呀，我又扯太远了
Look,I took it too far.
我以为你要去海滩
Hey,I thought you were going to the beach.
-又在下雨了 -什么？
- It's raining again. - What?
你瞧瞧吧
Would you look at that.
这星期以来 唯一有太阳的时候…
The only time the sun comes out the whole weekend..
就是我在演讲的那个小时
is the one hour I'm giving my speech.
那上头的某人还真喜欢我
Someone up there likes me.
但是下面的一些人都气死了
But people down here are pissed.
我不敢相信又在下雨了，真是不公平
I can't believe it's raining again. It's so unfair.
往好处想就是我们不用看到…
Well,on the bright side,now we won't have to see..
那些古生物学家脱掉上衣
all these paleontologists with their shirts off.
不是你们
Not you guys.
你们还不错
You've got it going on.
-我们今天要做什么呢？ -他们楼下有游戏间
- What will we do today? - They have a game room downstairs.
有兵乓球还有其他的东西
They have Ping-Pong and stuff.
乒乓球？亲爱的，他们有乒乓球耶
Ping-Pong? Honey,they have Ping-Pong.
-我们来玩 -我不要
- Let's play. - I don't think so.
-为什么不要？ -你知道你有多么得好胜
- Why not? - You know how competitive you get.
我以前说那样很可爱，可是 别人都不同意，而且我在说谎
And while I say it's cute,others disagree,and I'm lying.
-我又不是永远都那样糟糕 -是吗？
- I'm not always that bad. - Oh,yeah?
我们上次玩的时候发生什么事呢？
What happened when we played last time?
我揍了你
I punched you.
-还有呢？ -还有菲比
- And? - Phoebe.
-还有呢？ -我把你们的头撞在一起
- And? - I clunked your heads together.
-你在这里 -嘿，听着
- There you are. - Hey. Listen.
只要一停止下雨 我们一定要去潜水
As soon as it stops raining,we have got to go snorkeling.
有个小孩告诉我有海龟 如果你对着他的脸吹气泡…
Some kid told me about this sea turtle. If you blow bubbles in his face..
他会追着你跑喔
he chases you.
我很抱歉，我不能去 我整个下午都要主持一个讨论
I'm sorry,I can't. I'm running a discussion group all afternoon.
没关系，我找别人去好了
That's okay. I'll find someone else to do it.
我是可以一个人去，但是…
I'd do it alone,but..
我不知道海龟 如果抓到我会发生什么事
I don't know what happens if the sea turtle catches you.
我觉得很糟糕
You know,I feel so bad.
我整趟旅途都没有跟你在一起 尤其是昨晚…
I haven't seen you this whole trip. Especially last night..
不用担心，没关系 我跟瑞秋玩的很开心
Don't worry about it. It was fine. I had the best time with Rachel.
我只是为你难过 跟罗斯关在房间里赶演讲稿
I just felt bad for you,stuck in that room working on Ross' speech.
事实上，结果还蛮好玩的
Actually,it turned out to be a lot of fun.
那至少我们都过得很愉快，不是吗？
Oh,well,at least we're both having fun,right?
-我们不在一起却很快乐，很怪吧？ -是啊
- Is it weird that it's not with each other? - Yeah.
有一点，是啊
A little bit,yeah.
我想我们需要谈谈
I think we need to talk.
是啊，我想我们是需要
Yeah,I think we do.
谈什么呢？
About what?
-别这样，会很好玩的啦！ -好啦
- Come on,you guys,it'll be fun! - All right.
-不计分我才要玩 -那我们怎么知道谁赢呢？
- I'll play if we don't keep score. - Well,then how do we know who wins?
-没有人会赢 -所以我们是四个输家，超级的
- Nobody wins. - So we're just four losers. Super.
-我不要跟她玩 -我不要玩了
- Well,I'm not playing with her. - I'm out.
-我跟你玩 -好的
- I'll play you. - Okay.
-你不知道你在做什么 -她会很疯狂的
- You don't know what you're doing. - She gets crazy.
这个疤痕是从猜字游戏来的
This scar? That's from Pictionary.
我想我会没事的
I think I'll be all right.
-你想要先热身一下吗？ -当然，如果你想要的话
- You want to volley a bit for serve? - Sure,if you want to.
顺便说一下，我很厉害的
Oh,by the way,I'm awesome.
亲爱的上帝，他们俩是一样的
Oh,dear God,there's two of them.
-你准备好要玩了吗？ -当然了
- You ready to play? - Hell,yeah.
-你有看过他这一面吗？ -没有，我以为他跟你一样软弱
- Did you know this about him? - No idea. I thought he was soft like you.
-想要更好玩点吗？ -你想要多少呢？
- Want to make it more interesting? - How much you thinking?
-十块钱一局吗？ -加到五十块钱好了
- Ten bucks a game? - Make it 50.
-我加到一百块钱 -一千…
- I'll make it 100. - One thousand..
好了！
Okay!
我们掷铜板来决定谁先开球 你有铜板吗？
We'll flip to see who goes first. You got a quarter?
没有，你们两个女生谁有铜板呢？
No. Either of you girls got a quarter?
亲爱的，把这种骂人的话 都用到他身上
Honey,try to focus the trash talk on him.
-莫妮卡，你来猜 -正面，不，背面！正面！
- Monica,you call it. - Heads. No,tails! Heads!
-背面 -几率有这样低吗？
- Tails. - Oh,what are the chances?
-我得分！ -不，我可不这么认为
- My point! - Oh,no,I don't think so.
根据标准规定，若参赛者 在任何时间将没握球拍的手…
Standard rules: If at any time a player uses his nonracket-bearing hand..
碰触到球桌表面，将不算得分
to touch the playing surface,he or she forfeits the point.
他曾经是律师
He was a lawyer.
东岸的天气十分良好
All the East Coast is having beautiful weather.
在纽约是华氏七十二度 而且阳光普照
In New York,it's 72 and sunny.
气象婊子
Weather bitch.
门没锁
It's open.
-嗨，乔伊 -嘿
- Hi,Joe. - Hey.
-怎么了？一切都还好吗？ -查莉跟我分手了
- What? Is everything okay? - Charlie and I broke up.
不，为什么？
No. Why?
嗯，她说我们没有任何共同点
Well,she said we have nothing in common.
这真是胡说
That's crazy.
不，是真的，我们没有任何共同点
No,it's not. We have nothing in common.
-是啊，没错 -是啊
- Yeah,that's true. - Yeah.
她应该跟像是罗斯那样的人在一起
I mean,she should be with someone more like Ross.
你知道的 他也会用那些很难的字眼
You know,I mean he uses all those big words too.
-天啊，聪明的人真是无趣 -喂，嘿！
- Man,smart people are dull. - Well,hey!
得了吧，瑞秋
Okay,Rach.
我觉得好蠢，你知道吗？为什么我一直 都喜欢不适合我的女生呢？
I feel so stupid,you know? Why do I keep going after the wrong girls?
-你在说什么呢？ -喔，少来了
- What are you talking about? - Oh,come on.
我是说，有你，然后是查莉 这就像是…我到底是哪根筋不对呢？
I mean,there's you,then there's Charlie. It's like.. What the hell's my problem?
我只是…
I just..
或许你并没有都跟 不适合你的女生一起
Okay. Maybe you're not always going after the wrong girl.
我告诉你，瑞秋 查莉并不适合我
I'm telling you,Rach,Charlie is not right for me.
-我不是在说她 -是喔，那是谁呢？
- I'm not talking about her. - Well,then,who?
那个我上个月约过的女服务生吗？
The waitress I went out with last month?
-你知道吗？算了 -不…
- You know what? Forget it. - No,no,no,no.
-你是在说谁呢？ -不，我不…
- Who are you talking about? - No,I don't..
事实上我并不知道 我在说什么，所以…
I actually don't know who I'm talking about,so..
-好的 -嗯
- Okay. - Yeah.
我要去看看有没有办法 再订到另一间房间
Well,I'm gonna go see if I can get a room for tonight.
-待会见 -是啊，好的
- And I'll see you later. - Yeah,sure. Okay.
-你喜欢我？ -好吧
- You like me? - Okay.
-我们不要过度渲染这件事 -这是一件大事！
- Let's not make a big thing about this. - It's a huge thing!
你很不合作喔，乔伊
Okay,not working with me,Joe.
听着，事情是这样的 最近，我有些想法
Look,here's the thing. Lately,I have been having thoughts.
应该说是冥想
Musings,if you will.
-多久了呢？ -大概只有一个月
- Well,for how long? - Oh,only like a month.
-一个月？ -嗯…
- A month? - Well..
小声点，或许只是一些疯狂的想法 但是有时候我就是会想啊
Dial it down. Listen,maybe they're crazy thoughts,but sometimes I do.
我一直在想我们之间的可能性
I have been thinking about,you know,us.
-好的，现在音调提高一点 -你说的对，好的
- Okay,dial it up a little. - Oh,you're right. Okay.
-我只有一个问题 -该死
- I just have a question. - Shoot.
-你倒底是在做什么？ -我试着不要做任何事
- What the hell are you doing? - I'm not trying to do anything.
只是当我们在一起时非常地快乐 你知道吗？
It's just,we have such a good time when we're together,you know?
你难道都没有好奇过 那会是怎样吗？
And I mean,aren't you just a little curious what it would be like?
我好奇过？我就跟…
Am I curious? I mean,I'm as curious as..
乔治一样好奇！
George!
-谁？ -《好奇的乔治》啊！
- Who? - Curious George!
那只猴子还有那个戴黄帽的男人
You know,the monkey and the guy with the yellow hat.
-我当然记得 -他还有个纸路线图
- Of course. I remember. - He had a paper route.
是啊，没错
Yeah,he did.
-这就是我说的 -我知道，我们棒透了！
- See,this is what I'm talking about. - No,I know. We're great!
但是瑞秋，不，不能这样的
But,Rach,no,this can't happen.
不能有一点点机会吗？
Can't it just happen a little bit?
-不！一点也不行 -为什么不行？
- No! It can't happen at all! - Why not?
我最希望事情是这样了，好吗？
Because,look,no one wants this to happen more than me,okay?
我在我脑海中已经幻想过 这情节一百次了
I have gone over this moment in my head 100 times..
而且我从没拒绝过
and not once did I ever say no.
我不能这样对罗斯
I couldn't do it to Ross.
-但之前却不是这样 -我知道…
- But that wasn't gonna stop you before. - I know. I know..
但是在那之后我想了很多 这是不对的
but I've thought about it a lot since then,and it just wouldn't be right.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我也很抱歉
I'm sorry too.
-天啊，我不应该说出来的 -不…
- Oh,God,I shouldn't have said anything. - No,no.
别这样，我们没事的
No,no,no,no. Hey,we'll be fine.
-就像你所说的，这没有什么 -没错
- Like you said,it's no big deal. - It's not a big deal.
-没有什么 -真的是没有什么
- No big deal. - It's so not a big deal.
-待会见，好 -好的，太好了
- I'll see you later. All right,hey. - Okay,great.
好的…
Okay..
真抱歉喔，我想… 我想那可能没有碰到桌面
Oh,I'm sorry,I think.. I think that may have missed the table.
-是吗？ -是的
- Oh,do you? - Yeah.
- Do you? - Yeah.
-是吗？ -是的！
- Do you? - Yeah!
-你真的认为他这样很有魅力吗？ -是的
- You really find this attractive on him? - Oh,yeah.
你要告诉我你现在没有 被莫妮卡撩的心痒痒的？
Are you telling me you're not even a little turned on by Monica right now?
这是婚后我第一次觉得 我是比较有魅力的那一个
This is the first time in our marriage that I've felt like the more attractive one.
好了，加油，麦克，你可以打败她的
All right,come on,Mike. You can beat her.
把她打的落花流水
Knock that dog off her head.
-该死的！ -我跟他上床喔！
- Damn it! - I sleep with him!
-赛点 -别太骄傲
- Game point. - Don't get too cocky.
记住上次是我赢的
Remember,I won the last one.
喔，对了 输给一个女生感觉如何呢？
Oh,by the way,how did that feel,losing to a girl?
你应该先照照镜子再这样说
You should look in the mirror before you call yourself that.
-不！不！不！ -而就是这样结束了
- No! No! No! - And that's how it's done.
好了
Okey-dokey.
你们都各赢了一局 而我感觉好像是失去了一年的生命
You've each won a game,and I've lost what's felt like a year of my life.
每个人都可以跟一个赢家回家
Everybody goes home a winner.
-三战两胜？ -我就是这样想
- Best of three? - That's what I'm thinking.
我应该运用我的隐形术 来打击罪犯或是恶魔？
Should I use my invisibility to fight crime or for evil?
-开球吧，木头人 -“开球吧，木头人”
- Serve the ball,chump. - "Serve the ball,chump."
好的，重披战袍会更好，麦克 重披战袍会更好
Okay,better comebacks,Mike. Better comebacks.
我来接！
I got it!
顺便提一下，我没事！
I'm fine,by the way!
我是说我在阿尔刚金有间小木屋
I'm just saying,I have a cabin in the Adirondacks.
如果你有想要远离尘嚣 那会是…
If you ever want to get away from the city,well,that'd be..
很不错的
just nifty.
嗯，我现在事情是蛮多的
Well,I've kind of got a lot on my plate right now.
不是说我不喜欢 跟陌生男人到乡间度周末
Not that I wouldn't love a weekend in the country with a strange man.
-杰维斯？ -喔，你回来了
- Jarvis? - Oh,you're back.
-这是我老婆，南西 -少来了！
- This is my wife,Nancy. - Well,get out!
-罗斯，我可以跟你谈谈吗？ -当然了
- Ross? Can I talk to you for a minute? - Yes,please.
他还在看我吗？
Is he still looking at me?
是的
Yes.
-还在看吗？ -是的
- Still? - Yes.
而他老婆好像是在看我
And his wife's kind of looking at me.
发生什么事呢？
So,what's going on?
嗯，乔伊跟我分手了
Well,Joey and I broke up.
-我的天啊，发生了什么事？ -乔伊是个好男人
- Oh,my God. What happened? - Joey is a great guy..
但是我们就是… 我们很不一样了
but we're just.. We're so different.
就像是在你演讲的时候 他一直在笑“直立人”
I mean,like,during your speech,he kept laughing at "Homo erectus."
我就知道是他！
I knew that was him!
反正，我只是… 我想这样是最好的
Anyway,I just.. I think it's for the best.
-嘿，你还好吗？ -还好
- Hey. Hey,you okay? - I guess.
还有…
There was..
还有另外一个原因 让我跟乔伊分手的
There was another reason that I thought it was time to end it with Joey.
我开始发觉 我对另外一个人有感觉
I started to realize that I was having feelings for someone else.
好的，盖勒，研讨会的最后一天了
Okay,Geller. Last day of the conference.
你知道主讲人会被怎样的
You know what happens to the keynote speaker.
克雷克教授，我们正在谈话当中
Professor Klarik,we're in the middle of a conversation here.
-不能等会再丢他进游泳池吗？ -或是把你们俩都丢进去
- Can't you throw him in the pool later? - Or we could throw you both in now.
男士们，拜托，我们会不会太老了呢？
Okay,gentlemen,please. Aren't we a little old for this?
我是说我们是科学家，好吗？ 我们都有学术素养
I mean,we're scientists,all right? We're academics..
而且最重要的 你们必须要先捉住我们
and most importantly,you will have to catch us first.
跑！跑！跑！
Go! Go! Go!
好的，又平手了，四十一比四十一
Okay,so it's tied again,41 to 41.
-好的，听着，够了 -不
- Okay,look,enough is enough. - No.
-我剩下两分就可以打败他了 -莫妮卡，一小时前你就这样说了！
- I just have two more points to beat him. - Monica,that was also true an hour ago!
拜托，瞧瞧你自己
I mean,please,look at you.
你的手都起水泡了，你连站都站不住 你的头发真是莫名奇妙！
Your hand is blistered,you can barely stand,your hair is inexplicable!
菲比，去跟麦克说，帮我一下
Phoebe,talk to Mike. Help me out.
麦克，只要你赢，你将会享受到 你从未享受过的性爱
Mike,you win this,you will get the best sex you've ever had in your whole life.
好像是打击罪犯比较好
I say to fight crime.
你没有看到我们！
You didn't see us!
莫妮卡？
Monica?
你已经证明你跟他一样好了
You've already proven you're just as good as he is.
我们已经错过晚餐预约 所以我们就上楼去…
We missed our dinner reservations,so let's just go upstairs..
点客房服务，洗个澡 然后剃光你的头发！
order room service,take a shower and shave your head!
我不能这样走掉 我已经投入四小时了
I can't just walk away. I've put in four hours.
当你娶我的时候 你就知道我是这样的
You knew this about me when you married me.
你答应无论我生病 或是健康都要照顾我的
You agreed to take me in sickness and in health.
这就是我的病！
Well,this is my sickness!
-那洁癖呢？ -那只是好习惯
- What about the obsessive cleaning? - That's just good sense.
-你还好吗？ -亲爱的，我还好
- You okay? - No,honey,I'm okay.
甩一甩，噢，不能甩 不能甩，不能甩
Shake it off. Oh,no shaking. No shaking. No shaking.
我的天，我不能玩了
Oh,my God. I can't play.
-所以你要弃权？ -麦克赢了吗？
- So you forfeit? - Mike wins?
我不敢相信，我输了
I can't believe it. I lost.
-不，你没有 -什么？
- No,you didn't. - What?
-因为我要帮你玩 -你不能这样做
- Because I'm gonna play for you. - You can't do that.
没关系，我不在乎 到底是打败他们其中哪个
It's okay. I don't care which of them I beat.
好的，我们要把 那个球拍带回家，先生
Okay,we're taking that paddle home,mister.
-亲爱的，你没有必要这样做 -是的，我有必要
- Honey,you don't have to do this. - Yes,I do.
我或许无法理解 你为什么一定要赢…
I may not understand why you have to win so badly..
但是如果这对你很重要 对我就很重要
but if it's important to you,it's important to me.
因为我爱你
Because I love you.
但是你很逊啊
But you suck.
不客气，亲爱的
You're welcome,sweetheart.
好的，我们快玩吧，快点受死
All right,let's get this over with. Sudden death.
-赢得这一分的人就算赢了 -好的
- Whoever wins this point,wins. - Okay.
-天啊，你真棒 -这就像是看色情片一样
- Oh,my God. You're good. - It's like watching porn.
而这就是这样结束的
And that's how it's done.
我的天啊… 这实在太惊人了
Oh,my God. Oh,my God. That was so amazing.
嗯，你是何时…
Well,when did you..?
等等，我差点忘了，失败者
Hold on,I almost forgot. Loser.
-你是什么时候开始不逊的？ -我从来就不逊，我只是不想让你…
- When did you stop sucking? - I never sucked. I just didn't want you..
-知道我有多棒 -为什么？
- to know how good I was. - Why?
-我不知道 -这真是太棒了
- I don't know. - Well,this is so great.
-现在我们可以参加双打比赛了 -这就是为什么
- Now we can enter doubles tournaments. - That's why.
-他们还在找我们吗？ -是的
- They still looking for us? - Yeah.
吧台的人说他们分成两组搜索队伍
The bartender said they split up into two search parties.
草食性组跟肉食性组
The herbivores and the carnivores.
我们这一组并不是最酷的
You know,we,as a group,are not the coolest.
喔，小心
Oh,look out.
-我想他们没有看到我们 -没错
- I don't think they saw us. - I don't think they did.
身为研究家 他们并没有很认真的探索
You know,for a bunch of researchers,they sure don't look very carefully.
我刚刚要开始告诉你一些事
So I started to tell you something earlier.
还有其他的原因 让我跟乔伊分手的
There was another reason that I realized it was time to end it with Joey.
我有点惊觉到我开始对某人…
I kind of realized I was starting to have feelings..
有一些感觉
for someone else.
我可以问是谁吗？
And can I ask who?
我想你知道是谁
I think you know.
我想我也是，但过去我对这种事的判断 都是错的，所以…
I think I know too,but I've been really wrong about this stuff in the past,so..
-我很抱歉，我们不能 -好的，好的
- I'm sorry,we can't. - All right. All right.
我是说 你才刚跟我最好的朋友交往过
I mean,you just went out with my best friend,you know?
我只是认为这会是个很不好的主意
I just think it would be a really,really bad idea.
或许不会，我是说…
Or not. I mean..
什么？
What?